runehq.com 2017-01-18

# RuneHQ - RuneScape Help - Your Unfair RS Advantage

When you visit any of the many sites owned by Global Gaming HQ, LLC, we may collect and store information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. This information may include the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our sites, and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We may also record the name of your Internet service provider. We use this information only to measure site activity and to develop ideas for improving our sites. 

There are also several opportunities on our Web sites for you to provide us with information about you and your interests, such as your name, mailing address and email address. If you choose to share any personal information with us, we may store it and use it for marketing research and other marketing purposes. We may share this information with other companies that we do business with, such as advertisers. 

Personal information gathered and stored is given as statistics only (demographics), with no name or specific E-Mail address associated with it. We will never sell your actual personal information to any other company or identify your statistical information to other companies using your name or E-Mail address. 

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of our Web sites, such as chat rooms or bulletin boards, this information may be seen and used by others. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information on this site and in our forums. 

Some of our Web sites may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. So, when you come back to visit us again, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. 

You take online privacy seriously, and The Global Gaming HQ, LLC family of Web sites does too. It's our way of sustaining your trust in us, our products, and services. 

Global Gaming HQ and RuneHQ.com reserves the right to alter its privacy principles as business needs require. Any alterations to these principles will be posted on our Web sites in a timely manner. This privacy policy is applicable to all U.S.-based Global Gaming LLC Web sites. 

Many of the Web sites and online services we offer, as well as those of our partners, are supported by advertising. Through the Global Gaming HQ Advertising Platform, we may display ads on our own sites and the sites of our advertising partners. 

When we display online advertisements to you, we will place a one or more persistent cookies on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time we display an ad to you. The cookies we use for advertising have an expiry date of no more than 2 years. Because we may serve advertisements on many different Web sites, we are able to compile information over time about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements we display. We use this information to make predictions about your characteristics, interests or preferences and to display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate this information with your subsequent visit, purchase or other activity on participating advertisers’ Web sites in order to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements. 

While we may use some of the information we collect in order to personalize the ads we show you, we designed our systems to select ads based only on data that does not personally and directly identify you. For example, we may select the ads we display according to certain general interest categories or segments that we have inferred based on (a) demographic or interest data, including any you may have provided when creating an account (e.g. age, zip or postal code, gender), demographic or interest data acquired from other companies, and a general geographic location derived from your IP address, (b) the pages you view and links you click when using Global Gaming HQ’s and its advertising partners’ Web sites and services, and (c) the search terms you enter when using Global Gaming HQ’s Internet search services, such as Live SearchBing, and (d) information about the users you most frequently interact with through Global Gaming HQ’s communications or social networking services, such as Messenger.. For more information about how we target ads, visit Personalized Advertising from Global Gaming HQ. 

When we display personalized targeted ads, we take a number of steps designed to protect your privacy. For example, we store page views, clicks and search terms used for ad personalization targeting separately from your contact information or other data that directly identifies you (such as your name, e-mail address, etc.). Further, we have built in technological and process safeguards designed to prevent the unauthorized correlation of this data. We also give you the ability to opt-out of personalized targeted ads. For more information or to use the opt-out feature, you may visit our [opt-out page](https://admin.valueclickmedia.com/optout/index.html). In addition, you can go to the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), which offers a single location to opt-out of ad targeting from member companies. 

Although the majority of the online advertisements on Global Gaming HQ sites are displayed by Global Gaming HQ, we also allow third-party ad serving companies, including other ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites. These companies currently include, but are not limited to: [24/7 Real Media](http://www.247realmedia.com/), [aCerno,Inc](http://www.acerno.com/home.html), [AdBlade](http://www.adblade.com/), [AdConion](http://www.adconion.com/), [AdFusion](http://www.adfusion.com/), [Advertising.com](http://advertising.com/), [Bane Media](http://www.banemedia.com/), [Brand.net](http://www.brand.net/), [CasaleMedia](http://www.casalemedia.com/), [Collective Media](http://www.collective.com/), [Fox Interactive](http://roimediaconsultants.com/), [Interclick](http://www.interclick.com/), [Millennial](http://www.millennialmedia.com/), [PrecisionClick](http://www.precisionclick.com/), [ROI Media](http://roimediaconsultants.com/), [Social Media](http://www.socialmedia.com/), [SpecificMedia](http://www.specificmedia.com/), [TrafficMarketplace](http://www.trafficmarketplace.com/), [Tribal Fusion](http://www.tribalfusion.com/), [ValueClick](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/), and [YuMe](http://www.yumenetworks.com/).
